Guide to the Ahmad Nawash Collection AD.MC.094
al Mawrid Arab Art Archive, NYU Abu Dhabi
- Series VII: Photographs
  - VII.A. Exhibition Photographs
    - 5. Photographs of exhibitions at the University of Jordan. Circa 1970s, cuid330
    - 6. Photographs of exhibitions at the American Cultural Center, Amman. Circa 1970s, cuid331
    - 7. Solo exhibition at the University of Jordan, Amman, 1974, cuid332
    - 8. Solo exhibition at American Cultural Center, Amman, 1975, cuid333
    - 9. Solo exhibition at Library of University of Jordan, Amman, 1977, cuid334
    - 10. Solo exhibition at the French cultural Center, Amman, 1978, cuid335
    - 11. Solo exhibition at the French Cultural Center, Amman, 1979, cuid336
    - 12. Exhibitions at the American Cultural Center, Amman, 1970s, cuid337
    - 13. Solo exhibition at Jordan National Gallery for Fine Arts, 1981, cuid338
    - 14. Solo exhibition at the French Cultural Center, Amman 1983, cuid339
    - 15. Solo exhibition at the French Cultural Center, Amman 1987, cuid340
    - 16. Photographs of exhibitions, n.d., cuid341
    - 17. Queen Noor with Nawash at an exhibition opening in Amman, n.d., cuid342
  - VII.B. Photographs of Artworks, cuid343
    The series includes photographic prints of artworks by Ahmad Nawash taken in different periods and locations. Some photographs are black and white, and some have the artist's handwriting on the back, indicating the work's title.
  - VII.C. Personal Photographs, cuid344
    Collections of personal photographs of Ahmad Nawash while he studied in Rome in 1959 and in Italian cities such as Pisa circa the early 1980s. The series also includes pictures of the artist in different periods of his life and with fellow teachers graduating from the Amman Teachers' College in 1968-69.
  - VII.D. Photo Envelopes, cuid345
    Plastic and paper envelopes in which Nawsh kept his photographs and noted some information related to the content.